(Sheldon:)Because it's a hub.
(Amy:)Sheldon, can I come in?
(Sheldon:)-Do you have cookies?
-No.
(Sheldon:)Good. I don't deserve cookies.
Come in.
(Sheldon:)Wil?
(Wil Wheaton:)Hey, Sheldon.
It's been a while.
(Sheldon:)Why are you here?
(Wil:)Amy said you were
having a rough time,
(Wil:)and I thought maybe we could talk.
(Wil:)Is that okay?
(Sheldon:)Certainly.
(Sheldon:)Although... right now,
I'm having a rough time
(Sheldon:)because there's
three people in my room,
and its starting to feel
like a discotheque.
(Amy:)Sheldon, you said you were
unhappy getting attention
(Amy:)for something you wished
you never did.
(Wil:)Yeah, I know a little
something about that.
(Sheldon:)Oh, nonsense, Wil.
(Sheldon:)Your endless tweets
are not that bad.
(Wil:)I remember why it's been a while.
(Wil:)Sheldon, I was actually talking
(Wil:)about when I was a kid on Star Trek.
(Sheldon:)How could you not
like getting attention
(Sheldon:)for playing Wesley Crusher?
(Sheldon:)You were wonderful.
(Sheldon:)A know-it-all boy genius
with an eidetic memory.
(Sheldon:)Who couldn't relate to that?